hw.com 2010-12-31

# Privacy Statement

Harvard-Westlake School is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Harvard-Westlake School Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Harvard-Westlake School web site, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

### Collection of your Personal Information 

Harvard-Westlake School collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address or name. Harvard-Westlake School also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your preferences and interests.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Harvard-Westlake School. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Harvard-Westlake School for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Harvard-Westlake School Web site. 

### Use of your Personal Information

Harvard-Westlake School collects and uses your personal information to operate the Harvard-Westlake School Web site and deliver the services you have requested. We also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of services available from Harvard-Westlake School. 

Harvard-Westlake School does not sell, rent or lease its constituent lists to third parties. 

Harvard-Westlake School Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Harvard-Westlake School or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Harvard-Westlake School; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Harvard-Westlake School site, or the public.

### Use of Cookies

This web site uses "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Harvard-Westlake School pages, or register with Harvard-Westlake School site or services, a cookie helps Harvard-Westlake School to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your preferences, etc. When you return to the same Harvard-Westlake School Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the site’s features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Harvard-Westlake School services or Web sites you visit.

### Changes to this Statement

Harvard-Westlake School will occasionally update this Privacy Statement to reflect school and community feedback. Harvard-Westlake School encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Harvard-Westlake School is protecting your information.

### Contact Information

Harvard-Westlake School welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Statement. If you believe that Harvard-Westlake School has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Harvard-Westlake School at [techabuse@hw.com](mailto:abuse@hw.com).
